Handrub: eight steps, twenty to thirty seconds, covering every surface of both hands.
First, apply a palmful of handrub in a cupped hand.
Rub palm to palm.
Palm over the back of the other hand, fingers interlaced. Repeat on the other hand.
Palm to palm, fingers interlaced.
Backs of fingers to the opposite palm, fingers interlocked.
Rotate each thumb clasped in the other palm. Repeat on the other hand.
Rub the fingertips in circles on the other palm. Repeat on the other hand.
Finally, keep rubbing until dry — do not wipe.
Remember: in real life, the complete handrub takes only twenty to thirty seconds — not as long as this video.